<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital ramblings on Gerald</title>
    <link>/blahg/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital ramblings on Gerald</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 12:21:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blahg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Makefile</title>
      <link>/blahg/website_makefile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blahg/website_makefile/</guid>
      <description>Computers and software are wonderful things, instead of remembering to:
 Ensure all node packages are installed and/or up-to-date Compile css bits Generate the resume: markdown -&amp;gt; laTex -&amp;gt; laTex -&amp;gt; PDF Compile the static hugo site Add all of the changed files to the git repo Insert a helpful commit message to remember the work that was done Push the changes to master  In particular, I always seem to forget step 5 and end up with missing files since everything wasn&amp;rsquo;t appropriately staged before the commit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown resume</title>
      <link>/blahg/markdown_resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 12:18:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blahg/markdown_resume/</guid>
      <description> I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest, I hate maintaiting my resume and CV. There is something about opening your editor of choice fiddling with parameters, saving as a PDF, naming the file and uploading it somewhere that requires too many steps. It sure would be nice if we could use MarkDown to generate a PDF automagically whenever I press a new version of this website.
Pandoc and ConText to the rescue!
Markdown -&amp;gt; PDF  Pandoc is used to convert the Markdown file to a latex file ConText is then used to to convert the latex file to a pdf  Markdown -&amp;gt; html  Pandoc and a css style sheet can convert the resume markdown file to an html page  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Hugo</title>
      <link>/blahg/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 13:18:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blahg/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Testing out desiging a hugo theme. So far. So good.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>